lights go down to the stage another save you another cage
promises in bold
deadlines fade to black by deadline time said they'd fix
the writ in the warts
drain the swap and dream of forts but the only thing that
ever drains is rope
throwing down the campaign drains Brits of the Union bacon
switch every speech
another blitz they said the church was on their desk turns
out it was just a
press request hey wait wait that flag while they stuffed
your rights in a body
bag Epstein files must have lost them to be on the go bag
and Mary love of bottom
bricks the economy more like fixer books smoke and mirrors
photo ops dirty looks
student debt stoops change of that health care just a
bureaucratic trap and
every time they swear next herb they need next whether we
all learn crit W
Union smiling con red or blue same damn bond shake your
hand then rob you check
kiss your baby then break your neck we the people they say
with flair while
watching your lungs for billionaire dare a chicken every
pot lady if you invest
in the mobius portfolio and wear a bullet through fat so
the Union let it
spin every boats about you won't win hope for sale freedoms
least another
term another feast
you
hey hey democracy play scaring wires in suits with nothing
to say
grip W Union lights go black curtain drops they'll never
give it back